Preliminary Guide to the Washington State University College of Engineering Research Division Correspondence, Minutes, Reports, and Speeches circa 1940s-1970
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Preliminary Guide to the Washington State University College of Engineering Research Division Correspondence, Minutes, Reports, and Speeches
circa 1940s-1970
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
UA1983-04
Washington State University. College of Engineering. Research Division
45 Linear feet of shelf space 45 Boxes
Research files from the WSU Research Division the from 1940s to 1970. Includes research study files, investigative research, specimen preparation documents, and Model Experiments.
The Research Division of the College of Engineering was originally the Division of Industrial Research (DIR), established at Washington State University in 1946. The DIR conducted studies and research leading toward the economical use of material resources in the Northwest and the broad, well-balanced development of the state. The DIR was reorganized in 1966 under the College of Engineering. Dr. E. W. Greenfield was the director of the Research Division from 1966 until 1972 when Dr. George Marra took over as head, until his retirement in 1980.
Research files from the WSU Research Division from the 1940s-1970. Includes Research study files, Investigative research, specimen preparation documents, Model Experiments, miscellaneous files, and budget files. A preliminary item by item guide exists to boxes 1-45.
This is an unprocessed collection. Any arrangement reflects either a pre-existing order from the records' creators or previous custodians, or preliminary sorting performed by staff.
Items remain in their original order. Some folders are labeled and dated while others contain no date. A preliminary item by item list exists and is included in this guide.
This collection is open and available for research use.
This material was transferred to WSU Libraries' MASC by Nick Staba and Steve Garl of the College of Engineering on March 15, 1983 and retained as UA1983-04.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Washington State University. College of Engineering. Research Division -- Records and correspondence
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities
- Research Report on the Isolation and Purification of Humulone and Lupulone from Mature Hops, G.G. Smith (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Hydraulic Building Plans (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Ontario Hydro Research News (July-Sept., 1952) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Special Tests on Digtomite (Box 2, Folder 4)
- IPC Analysis (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Effect of Salt Water on the Tensile Strength of Koppers Jet Set, Bitumastic #100 and Bitumastic (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Investigation of Five Retardant Treatments for Particle Board (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Investigation of Five Retardant Treatments for Particle Board (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Preparation of Douglas-fir Specimens (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Analysis of Swedish Steel Rock Bit (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Photomicrographic Study of Cement and Hydrated Portland Cement (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Corrosion Steel Water Main (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Police Investigation (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Chemical Analysis of Oil Residue and Ash (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Analysis of Moisture Proofing Compound (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Water Analysis (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Manufacture of Three-layer Particle Boards (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Reduction of Dry-Lab Fiber and Toilet Tissue to Flock Form (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Value and Elbow Calibration Tests (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Arson - Butte, Montana (Box 2, Folder 20)
- IR, VV, X-ray and Emission Spectra on Submitted Organic Chemicals (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Possible Arson at Lindley Hall, University of Idaho (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Problem Analysis of the Moses Lake Gr and Water Supply (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Analyzer Study of Moses Lake upply System (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Network Analysis of the Water System of the City of Moses Lake (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Arson - Harlowton, Montana (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Arson - Harlowton, Montana (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Advisory Panel on Undergraduate Research (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Investigation of Arizona Ponderosa Pine for Hardboard (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Investigation of Arizona Ponderosa Pine for Hardboard (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Comparison of Experimental Pine Hardboard with Commercial Standards (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Tests on Paper Clay (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Drill Log Descriptions (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Descriptions of Drill Cuttings Obtained by the Simplot Co. (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Tests on Heavy Mastic Coatings (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Tests on Heavy Mastic Coatings (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Flapreg Plaques for N.N. Wood Products Clinic (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Analyze Lead Metal (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Analyze Lead Metal (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Standard Rubber Tests on Winter Tread "Camel Back" (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Tests on Winter Tread "Camel Back" (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Construct one Ergograph (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Intake Gates Priest Rapids (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Intake Gates Priest Rapids (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Flaking Miscellaneous Hardwoods (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Rocking Tests of Particle Board Panels (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Evaluation of "Par-Tex" Particle Board for Sheathing Applications (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Lubricating Oil and Grease Specifications (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Lubricating Oil and Grease Specifications (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Diesel Fuel Oil Specifications Survey (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Hit-Run Paint Comparison (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Development of Improved Automobile Grease (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Polynuclear and Halogen Compounds As Industrial Grease Additives (Box 2, Folder 53)
- A Study of the Application of Geochemical Methods to the Location of Ore Bodies in Pend Oreille County (Box 2, Folder 54)
- A Study of the Application of Geophysical and Geochemical Methods to the Location of Ore Bodies in Pend Oreille County (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Geochemical and Resistivity Prospecting Methods (Box 2, Folder 56)
- A Study of the Application of Geophysical and Geochemical Methods to the Location of Ore Bodies in Pend Oreille County, Wash. (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Spectrographic Analyses of Water Residues (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Spectrographic Analyses of Water Residues (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Evaluation of Particle Board Underlayment (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Preliminary Evaluation of Particle Board for Sheathing (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Comparison of the mechanical Properties of Inland- and Coast-Type Douglas Fir and Wester Larch Plywood (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Identification of White Liquor Sludge (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Identification of White Liquor Sludge - Potlach Forests, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Evaluation of Lock Deck Panels and Certification of Test Procedures (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Analysis of Green Sludge and Ash (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Analysis of Green Sludge and Ash (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Spectographic Analysis of Ash (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Evaluation of Experimental Larch Plywood (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Evaluation of Experimental Larch Plywood (Box 2, Folder 70)
- 50" Hydraulic Press Rental (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Identification of White Liquor Sludge (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Analysis of Welding Flux (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Relative Gloss pf Experimental Paper (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Quarterly Cost and Income Reports 1962/63 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Diesel Fuel Oil Investigation (Box 2, Folder 75)
- American Society of Civil Engineers - Hydrochemicals Meeting - Hydraulic Division (Box 2, Folder 76)
- ASCE Hydromechanics Committee Meeting (Box 2, Folder 77)
- A Study of the Beneficiation of Beryllium Ores (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Arden Dairy Company (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Analysis of Metal Samples (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Police Investigation (Homicide) (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Investigation of the Effect of Calcium Chloride in Construction (I) (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Investigation of Air Bubble Stability (Box 2, Folder 83)
- Round Butte Hydroelectric Dev. Trifurcation Structure- Model Studies for Tie Bar (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Wells Flume Model (Bechtel Corporation) (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Hydraulic Model Studies Chungju Hydroelectric Project (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Hydraulic Model Studies Chungju Hydroelectric Project (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Wells Hydroelectric Project Sectional Spillway Model Studies (Box 2, Folder 88)
- Wells Hydroelectric Project Sectional Spillway Model Studies (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Hydraulic Model Studies - Boundary Project (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Wells Flume Model Bechtel Corporation (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Water System Analysis - Las Cruces, New Mexico (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Packwood Drop Structure (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Sultan River Project, Dam No. 1 (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Recent European Practice in Design of Intakes Located in Debris-Carrying Streams (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Mcllroy Analysis of Water Distribution System for Bellingham, Washington (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Consultant Services - Chemical Slurry Pump Design and Lubrication (Box 3, Folder 97)
- Gas Flow and Heat Transfer Consultation Service (Box 3, Folder 98)
- Hydraulic Model Studies of Downcomers (Box 3, Folder 99)
- Hydraulic Model Studies of Downcomers (Box 3, Folder 100)
- Plastic Impregnated Gavels (Box 3, Folder 101)
- Properties of Lignin Compositions (Box 3, Folder 102)
- Thermal Conductivity of Castable Refractories (Box 3, Folder 103)
- Experimental Drying of Monoglyceride Emulsions (Box 3, Folder 104)
- Consultation on Patent Application (Box 3, Folder 105)
- Review and respond on patent application (Box 3, Folder 106)
- Hell's Canyon Model Studies (Box 3, Folder 107)
- Weatherometer Study on Fiberglass Sections for Swimming Pool (Box 3, Folder 108)
- Reclamation of Cathode Asbestos (Box 3, Folder 109)
- Reclamation of Cathode Asbestos (Box 3, Folder 110)
- Reclamation of Cathode Asbestos (Box 3, Folder 111)
- Isolation of Pollen Allergens Progress Report #4 (Box 3, Folder 112)
- Studies on Isolation of Active Allergy Components from Pollen (Box 3, Folder 113)
- Process Ragweed Pollen to Obtain Allergenic Components (Box 3, Folder 114)
- Police Investigation, Idaho County (Box 3, Folder 115)
- Arson Investigation (Box 3, Folder 116)
- Carbon Dating of Archeological Samples (Box 3, Folder 117)
- Carbon Dating of Archeological Samples (Box 3, Folder 118)
- Inv. of Grinding Characteristics of Aluminum Sinter (Box 3, Folder 119)
- Carbon Dating of Charcoal and Shell (Box 3, Folder 120)
- Carbon Dating of Charcoal (Box 3, Folder 121)
- Carbon Dating of Charcoal (Box 3, Folder 122)
- Carbon Dating of Archeological Samples (Box 3, Folder 123)
- All Sky Camera Observations During IGC-1959 (Box 3, Folder 124)
- Preparation of Air Pollution Instrumental Monograph (Box 3, Folder 125)
- Evaluation of Molded Particleboard Cases (Box 3, Folder 126)
- Evaluation of Molded Particleboard Beverage Cases (Box 3, Folder 127)
- Bagasses Fiberboard (Box 3, Folder 128)
- Arson Investigation (Box 3, Folder 129)
- Police Investigation - Kittitas County (Box 3, Folder 130)
- Police Investigation (Box 3, Folder 131)
- Density Control with Nuclear Equipment (Box 3, Folder 132)
- Detailed Study of Chemical Composition of Steam Condensate from Dry Kiln (Box 3, Folder 133)
- Supplemental Seismic Studies (Box 3, Folder 134)
- Geographical Well Logging (Box 3, Folder 135)
- Analyze Seven Suspect Drug Samples (Box 3, Folder 136)
- Water Analysis, Coulee Dam National Recreation Area (Box 3, Folder 137)
- Coincidental Features of Certain VLF Emissions, HF Cosmic **and Auveval Noise, and Ultra HF Solar Emission (Box 3, Folder 138)
- Coincidental Features of Certain Natural Radio Noise Emissions (Box 3, Folder 139)
- Coincidental Features of Certain VLF Emissions, HF Cosmic **and Aureral Noise, and Ultra HF Solar Emission (Box 3, Folder 140)
- Nelsonite as an Additive for Particleboard (Box 3, Folder 141)
- Ionispheric Research (Box 3, Folder 142)
- WSU Carbon-14 Dating Subsidy (Box 3, Folder 143)
- Effects of Benthos on Decomposition (Box 3, Folder 144)
- Recovery of Marketable products from Magnesite Flue Dust (Box 3, Folder 145)
- Evaluation of Industrial Coatings (Box 3, Folder 146)
- Atmospheric Science Facility - Recorders (Box 3, Folder 147)
- Audio Analysis of Selected Words (Box 3, Folder 148)
- Feasibility Study of the Post Bonding of Carbon-Reinforced Plastics (Box 3, Folder 149)
- Age Dating of Pend Oreille Mine and Surface Waters (Box 3, Folder 150)
- Show-Through Evaluation of Particleboard with High- Density Overlay (Box 3, Folder 151)
- Laminating Plexiglass (Box 3, Folder 152)
- Evaluation of Particleboard for Show-through Prop.- Rock Island Millwork Co. (Box 3, Folder 153)
- Study of Lower Snake River Water Temperatures (Box 3, Folder 154)
- Study of Oil Lubricated Instrument Bearing Storage (Box 3, Folder 155)
- Storage and Torque Evaluation of Oil Lubricated Instrument Bearings (Box 3, Folder 156)
- Storage and Torque Evaluation of Oil Lubricated Instrument Bearings (Box 3, Folder 157)
- Storage and Torque Evaluation of Oil Lubricated Instrument Bearings (Box 3, Folder 158)
- Storage and Torque Evaluation of Oil Lubricated Instrument Bearings (Box 3, Folder 159)
- Storage and Torque Evaluation of Oil Lubricated Instrument Bearings (Box 3, Folder 160)
- Storage and Torque Evaluation of Oil Lubricated Instrument Bearings (Box 3, Folder 161)
- Storage and Torque Evaluation of Oil Lubricated Instrument Bearings (Box 3, Folder 162)
- Storage and Torque Characteristics Research of Oil Lubricated Instrument Bearings (Box 3, Folder 163)
- Libby Air Quality Survey (Box 3, Folder 164)
- Air Quality Study - Libby, Montana - Final Report (Box 3, Folder 165)
- Hydraulic Studies of Clay Slurry Flow Characteristics (Box 3, Folder 166)
- Round-the-World Ratio Propagation Studies (Box 3, Folder 167)
- Northwest Aluminum Co. Air Quality Study (Box 3, Folder 168)
- Develop Field Method for Analysis of Animal Dip Solutions (Box 3, Folder 169)
- Accelerated Weathering Tests (Box 3, Folder 170)
- Formulation of Light Weight Aggregate Concrete Mix (Box 3, Folder 171)
- Clarence E. Simpson (Box 3, Folder 172)
- Short Course in Non-destructive Testing (Box 3, Folder 173)
- Consultation with Simpson Timber Co. (Box 3, Folder 174)
- Manufacturing Variables for Redwood Particle Board (Box 3, Folder 175)
- Production of Large Experimental Exterior Redwood Flakeboards (Box 3, Folder 176)
- Feasibility Study on Vacuum Forming of Plastic Device (Box 3, Folder 177)
- Impression Finger Jointing of South African Pine (Box 3, Folder 178)
- DIR Architectural Engineering Research Station (Box 4, Folder 179)
- Chemical Engineering Section (Box 4, Folder 180)
- Chemical Engineering Department Research Section (Box 4, Folder 181)
- DIR Chemistry Section (Box 4, Folder 182)
- Design Section (Box 4, Folder 183)
- Engineering Experimental Station (Box 4, Folder 184)
- Electrical Engineering Department Research Section (Box 4, Folder 185)
- Highways Research Section (Box 4, Folder 186)
- Hydraulics Section (Box 4, Folder 187)
- Mechanical Engineering Department Research Section (Box 4, Folder 188)
- Metallurgy Section (Box 4, Folder 189)
- Mining Experiment Station (Box 4, Folder 190)
- Sanitary Research Section (Box 4, Folder 191)
- Spectroscopy Section (Box 4, Folder 192)
- Vibrations and Applied Mechanics Section (Box 4, Folder 193)
- Wood Technology Section (Box 4, Folder 194)
- Technical Extension Services - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 195)
- Technical Extension - Short Courses and Conferences (Box 4, Folder 196)
- **Technical Extension - Inst. Tech. Publications (Box 4, Folder 197)
- Technical Extension "News Items" (Box 4, Folder 198)
- College of Engineering - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 199)
- College of Engineering Finance and Budget (Box 4, Folder 200)
- College of Engineering - Agricultural Engineering Department (Box 4, Folder 201)
- Agricultural Engineering Department - Farm Electrification Committee (Box 4, Folder 202)
- Architectural Engineering Department (Box 4, Folder 203)
- Chemical Engineering Department (Box 4, Folder 204)
- Civil Engineering Department (Box 4, Folder 205)
- Sanitary Engineering Advisory Committee (Box 4, Folder 206)
- Electrical Engineering Department (Box 4, Folder 207)
- Mechanical Engineering Department (Box 4, Folder 208)
- Aeronautical Engineering - Instructions (Box 4, Folder 209)
- Nuclear Engineering Department (Box 4, Folder 210)
- Weather Modification Proposal (Box 4, Folder 211)
- Creep Behavior of Polyethylene (Box 4, Folder 212)
- Aural Analysis of Material Under Stress (Box 4, Folder 213)
- Combustion Facility - Mechanical Engineering (Box 4, Folder 214)
- Two Phase Flow (Box 4, Folder 215)
- Effect of Thyrocalcification on Bone Structure (Box 4, Folder 216)
- Field Transducers for Electrical Measurements (Box 4, Folder 217)
- Improving Transportation for Washington State University (Box 4, Folder 218)
- Evaluation of Load Bearing Capacity of Flexible Pavements (Box 4, Folder 219)
- Improving Highway Legislation (Box 4, Folder 220)
- Improving Public Works Administration (Box 4, Folder 221)
- Water Resources Atlas of the State of Washington (Box 4, Folder 222)
- Mixing of High Velocity Flows (Box 4, Folder 223)
- Channel Degradation Below Hydraulics Structures (Box 4, Folder 224)
- Stream Craging Weirs for Reynolds Creek Watershed (Box 4, Folder 225)
- Hydropower (Box 4, Folder 226)
- Slurries and Non-Newtonian Flows (Box 4, Folder 227)
- Thermal Problems in Reservoirs (Box 4, Folder 228)
- River Engineering (Box 4, Folder 229)
- Hydrogeologic Investigation of Well ARH-DCI (Box 4, Folder 230)
- HydrJogical Investigations (Box 4, Folder 231)
- Radiation Heat Transfer in High Temperature Gases (Box 4, Folder 232)
- Steady Flow Combustion Facility Phase I (Box 4, Folder 233)
- Design and Construction of Ballistic Test Stand (Box 4, Folder 234)
- Noise Pollution Chapter for Handbook (Box 4, Folder 235)
- The Influence of Surface Emmissivity on Conduction, Convection, and Radiation in a Non-isothermal Hydrogen Hydrogen Plasma (Box 4, Folder 236)
- Strain-Aging in Neutron Irradiated Molybdenum (Box 4, Folder 237)
- Dimensional Dependence of Newtonian Creep (Box 4, Folder 238)
- Vacuum Furnace Assembly (Box 4, Folder 239)
- Biological Impact of Combined Metallic and Organic Pollution in the Cour D'Alene Lake River System (Box 4, Folder 240)
- Mason County Lake Study (Box 4, Folder 241)
- Survival of Intestinal Bacterial in Pristine Waters (Box 4, Folder 242)
- Dispersion of Aerosolized Bacteria During Manure Slurry Application (Box 4, Folder 243)
- Palouse Water Quality Survey (Box 4, Folder 244)
- Atomic Absorption Spectrophotometry in Water and Wastewater Analysis (Box 4, Folder 245)
- Treatment of Potato Products Wastes (Box 4, Folder 246)
- Evaluation on Solid Waste Disposal (Box 4, Folder 247)
- Nutrient Removal from Waste Water Systems (Box 4, Folder 248)
- Eutrophication in Recreation Lakes (Box 4, Folder 249)
- Bioassays to Determine Algal Growth Potential of Micronutrients (Box 4, Folder 250)
- Cooperative Interstate Study - Air Pollution Effects Network (Box 4, Folder 251)
- Fluoride Specific Microelectrodes (Box 4, Folder 252)
- Research Outline on Plant Volatiles (Box 4, Folder 253)
- Fluoride Analysis of Carrot Leaves (Box 4, Folder 254)
- Spokane Limed Filter Paper Data (Box 4, Folder 255)
- Spokane Limed Filter Paper Data (Box 4, Folder 256)
- Survey of Washington State Process Industries (Box 4, Folder 257)
- Fire Properties of Materials for Construction and Public Use (Box 4, Folder 258)
- Analytical Services Laboratory (Box 4, Folder 259)
- Trace Elements in Biological Fluids (Box 4, Folder 260)
- Wood Extractives (Box 4, Folder 261)
- Post Curing by Electrical Induction Heating (Box 4, Folder 262)
- Accelerated Weathering of Exterior Coating And Components (Box 4, Folder 263)
- Arabinogalactan: A Flotation Reagent (Box 4, Folder 264)
- WSU PNW Plastics Workshop (Box 4, Folder 265)
- The Ionic Polymerization of Benzaldehyde and Benzaldehyde Derivates (Box 4, Folder 266)
- Dependence of Piezoelectric Properties in Polythylenes on Polymer Crystallinity (Box 4, Folder 267)
- WSU PNW Plastics Workshop (Box 4, Folder 268)
- Post-Bonding of Plastics Reinforcements (Box 4, Folder 269)
- Arabinogalactan-phenol Structure (Box 4, Folder 270)
- Electrical Thermal Bonding of Polymers onto Minerals (Box 4, Folder 271)
- Fiscal Information 7/1/68 - 6/31/69 (Box 4, Folder 272)
- Section Budgets - 1970/1971 (Box 4, Folder 273)
- Section Budget Forecasts 7/11/71 (Box 4, Folder 274)
- Section Budget Forecasts 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 275)
- 197/71 Midyear Budget Revisions (Box 4, Folder 276)
- Section Budgets 1970/71 - Jan. 1, 1971 Revision (Box 4, Folder 277)
- Quarterly Costs and Income Reports 1964/65 (Box 5, Folder 278)
- Section Budget Forecast 1960/61 Start of Year (Box 5, Folder 279)
- Section Annual Budget Forecasts 1961/62 (Box 5, Folder 280)
- Original Section Budgets 1968/69 (Box 5, Folder 281)
- Budget Allocation 1962/63 July 1, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 282)
- Budget Allocation 1961/62 January 2, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 283)
- Budget Allocation 1961/62 January 2, 1962 (Desk Copy) (Box 5, Folder 284)
- Budget Allocation 1962-1963 July 1, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 285)
- Budget Allocation 1962-1963 January 1, 1963 (Desk Copy) (Box 5, Folder 286)
- Budget Allocation 1962-1963 January 1, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 287)
- Budget Allocation 1963-1964 July 1, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 288)
- Section Budgets 1963-1964 Desk Copy (Box 5, Folder 289)
- Budget Allocation 1963-1964 Jun. 2, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 290)
- Allocated Budgets by Section 1964/65 Desk Copy July 1, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 291)
- Authorized Budgets 1964/65 Desk Copy - 6/1/64 (Box 5, Folder 292)
- Budget Allocation - June 30, 1964 to July 1, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 293)
- New Budgets 1965/66 (Box 5, Folder 294)
- Section Budgets for July 1, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 295)
- 1965-1966 Budget Forecast Mid-year revision 1/1/66 (Box 5, Folder 296)
- Application for Civil Engineer Block Research Section (Box 6, Folder 297)
- Applications for Chemical Engineer (Box 6, Folder 298)
- Applications for General Analytical Chemist (Box 6, Folder 299)
- Application for Organic Chemist (Box 6, Folder 300)
- Applications for Design Engineer (ME) (Box 6, Folder 301)
- Application for Electronics Engineer (Box 6, Folder 302)
- Application for Electronics Engineer (Box 6, Folder 303)
- Applications for Extractive Metallurgist (Box 6, Folder 304)
- Sanitary Job (Box 6, Folder 305)
- Use of College Names in Advertising (Box 6, Folder 306)
- Oil Analysis 10/26/60 (Box 7, Folder 307)
- Referee Water Analysis (Box 7, Folder 308)
- ** Investigate causes of crack formation in the pastic body body of ammonia applicator pumps Trade name (Box 7, Folder 309)
- Study of Potentials Resulting from Pressure Gradient in Liquids, NSF (Box 7, Folder 310)
- The Advance of A Shallow Liquid Front Down a Dry Channel (Box 7, Folder 311)
- Arabogalactan From Larch, Extraction and Purification (Box 7, Folder 312)
- Temperature Effect on the Extraction of Arabogalactan from Larch Wood (Box 7, Folder 313)
- Explosive Hazard of Arabogalactan from Larch Dust (Box 7, Folder 314)
- Proposed Program for the Continuation of Studies on **St Ractum during 1962 ?? (Box 7, Folder 315)
- Heat Transfer in Arabogalactan Solutions (Box 7, Folder 316)
- The Emulsifying Properties of Arabogalactan (Box 7, Folder 317)
- Arabogalactan from Larch Wood (Box 7, Folder 318)
- Physical Properties of Arabogalactan (Box 7, Folder 319)
- Studies of the 4" Diameter Column Pilot Plant (Box 7, Folder 320)
- Studies on Physical Properties and Impurities of Arabogalctan Extracts (Box 7, Folder 321)
- Arabogalactan from Larch - Adjusted Budget for Third Quarter, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 322)
- Arabogalactan Cost Estimate (Box 7, Folder 323)
- Revised Cost Estimate 1000 Pound Per Day Arabogalactan Pilot Plant (Box 7, Folder 324)